http://liveworkplay.com.au/privacy-policy/

Liveworkplay.com.au.com Privacy Policy
Collecting of InformationLiveworkplay.com.au is committed to protecting your privacy when you visit our web site. You can access LiveWorkPlay.com.au and browse our site without disclosing any of your personal information. We do collect your name and email address if you request to receive our newsletter or purchase any goods and only use the details for sending our newsletter and processing purchase of goods.
Disclosure of InformationLiveworkplay.com.au will not sell, trade or rent your personal information to other parties. We may collect IP addresses to compile statistics about our visitors and traffic patterns but do not include personal identifying information.
External web sitesLiveworkplay.com.au contains links to other web sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of these other sites. You are encouraged to check each web sites privacy policy.
Affiliate DisclaimerLiveworkplay.com.au has financial relationships with a number of companies/organisations mentioned in our website. Liveworkplay.com.au may be compensated if you book and/or purchase a product/service from one of these affiliates. We endeavour to advise you when we have an affiliate link on a page.
Transactional InformationIf you purchase products or services from our shop on Liveworkplay.com.au, we will collect certain information from you in order to fulfil the order including your name, address, email address and information about the product or service you are purchasing. Payments are processed by a third-party (PayPal) so please refer to their terms and privacy policy for more information about how they process and store payment information.
AdsLiveworkplay.com.au may partner with third-party advertisers and ad networks to provide targeted content to your interests. These third parties may collect information sent from your computer, browser or mobile device. We suggest you check their privacy policies of how they will use any such information.
Analytics PartnersLiveworkplay.com.au uses analytics partners (Google Analytics) to help analyse usage and traffic for our Services, such as the number of unique visitors to our site. This information is not shared.
Other InformationYou may choose to provide other information directly to us by email requesting customer support or information. We do not use the information in any way that it is not intended for. For example, if we run a competition we may need to collect certain information such as name and email address to advise of and contact winners.
Our Commitment to Children’s PrivacyProtecting the privacy of the young is important to us. Our site is aimed at people 18 years and over and for this reason we do not collect or maintain information on anyone under 18.
ChangesLiveworkplay.com.au may change this Privacy Policy from time to time but if you continue to visit and use our Services/Products after Privacy Policy changes then you consent to the revised policy.
Contact UsAny questions please email sharyn@liveworkplay.com.au
